(Penny:)I get it. Leonard has no business
being involved with a waitress/actress...
(Penny:)...who felt so insecure, that she lied to him
about finishing community college.
(Sheldon:)Why would you lie about that?
He was going on about this college
and that grad school...
(Penny:)...and I didn't want him to think
I was some kind of stupid loser.
You thought the opposite of "stupid loser"
was "community-college graduate"?
(Penny:)There are a lot of successful people
in this country...
...who are community-college graduates.
Yeah, but you are neither.
(Penny:)Right. Okay, look,
this is between you and me.
(Penny:)You cannot tell Leonard any of this.
- You're asking me to keep a secret?
- Yeah.
(Sheldon:)Well, I'm sorry.
You would've had to express that desire
before revealing the secret...
...so that I could choose whether I wanted
to accept the covenant of secret-keeping.
(Sheldon:)You can't impose a secret
on an ex post facto basis.